<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Italian Metabolomics Network</title>
    <link>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Italian Metabolomics Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/mission/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/mission/mission/</guid>
      <description>The ITALIAN METABOLOMICS NETWORK is a home for all researchers active in the field of metabolomics in Italy. The Network is open to everybody, no matter the research topic, or the technique used, or the professional level, or the background, or the affiliation. If the investigation of the metabolome is part of your everyday work (and passion), then you are welcome to join!
The participation to the network is free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To become a member</title>
      <link>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/join/joinus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/join/joinus/</guid>
      <description>Our objective is to make the Network as open and flexible as possible. Every researcher/professional active in the field of metabolomics is welcomed.
 Membership is free of charge The name of the associates and their affiliation will be displeyed on the network website Members will be automatically added to the Network newsletter  To join the network Contact by e-mail one of the promoters sending a request of association. The e-mail should include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us!</title>
      <link>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/main/inevidenza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pietrofranceschi.github.io/MetabolomicsNetwork/main/inevidenza/</guid>
      <description>The Italian Metabolomics Network aims to bring together people with different backgrounds actively working in the field of metabolomics, and more broadly in the study of metabolism.
The objective is to promote networking, by offering opportunities for discussion, collaboration, training and exchanges between the participants.
The Network is open to everybody, no matter the research topic, the technique, the background, or the affiliation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>